Good morning, Mr. Henderson.
Good morning, teacher.
Would you like some tea?
Yes, please.
It has been a long time since
you taught elementary students.
How is this year going?
The students have a lot of potential.
I heard you gave out a Tonito already
on the first day?
It was a rare occurrence
for the prestigious Eden Academy.
It's the first I've heard of
such an incident.
It's only a fair ruling.
Good deeds are praised,
and misconduct is punished accordingly.
That is the essence of education.
You're absolutely right.
Young students who pass through
the gates of Eden,
will carry on and preserve traditions
as they learn to be elegant every day.
Our school exists to make
the future of this country elegant.
Mr. Damian!
Isn't this your brother?
Yeah…
It's your brother's entrance ceremony!
He's probably pictured elsewhere too!
-Oh, there!
-Oh!
Here too!
He's an MVP here!
Your brother is receiving Stellas
at an incredible rate! How amazing!
But Damian, I'm sure you'll become
an Imperial Scholar even faster!
I'm sure you'll receive the first Stella
in our grade!
I… I guess…
But we still have some time
before the exams…
Your first chance will be…
CLASS COMPETITION WITH DODGEBALL
Next week's Physical Education class!
There will be
an intergroup dodgeball tournament!
Oh!
So this is something my friend heard
from his friend in Class Seven, but…
apparently if you become the MVP,
you'll receive a Stella!
Really?
This is it, Mr. Damian!
An MVP, huh?
The weather is beautiful. Boys and girls.
Today, you are going to succeed a new page
in the history of Eden Academy.
Elegantly and brilliantly.
Shut up, you started fighting us first!
-It's not Anya's fault.
-She's right! In fact, you--
-Shut up, ugly!
-Huh?!
-Bastard.
-Who are you speaking to, Short Legs?!
You can't say that to girls!
Elega… nt.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
-Anya's home!
-Welcome home, Anya!
Father! I got some big news for you!
What?
You can receive a Stella at the next
Physical Education class?
Becky said so.
My friend heard from
her friend in Class Seven that…
rumor has it that the MVP of the class
that wins next week's tournament
will be awarded a Stella!
A rumor… That sounds doubtful…
Then we'll have to train, Anya!
Train!
So, what's the event
you'll be competing in?
Dodgeball.
Dodgeball…
It's the game where you hit the opponent
with a ball and bury them, right?
What does she mean by "bury"?
Mother, teach me your killer moves!
Okay!
I'll teach you
my killer one-ball technique!
Are you good at sports too, Yor?
Oh, no. I've only played catch
with my brother in the past.
I can't tell him that I rip up
and throw humans on a daily basis!
Leave it to me, Anya!
We'll catch a star with the killer move!
Anya will get a star with dodgeball!
Star Catching Anya will do her best!
-I'm happy that she's optimistic, but…
-Star Catching Super Anya!
That's right.
First, we start with muscle training.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Stamina is important too!
Anya!
Remember,
you can't throw a ball
with arm strength alone.
You have to step out firmly,
twist your hips
while shifting your weight,
transfer the force
to your shoulders, and throw like this!
Now, let's try!
Oh, Loid!
This is training?
I don't really get it,
but I'm leaving this one to Yor.
Wake up, Anya.
-Ha!
-Wham!
-Hmph!
-Snap!
-Pow!
-Ha!
Anya will catch a star tomorrow!
Anya did her best!
I endured
Mother's relentless training too.
I even thought of a name
for my killer shot.
Anya will catch a star!
I'll get a lot of stars
and help Father with his mission!
You sure are full of motivation.
Just don't get in the way
of Mr. Damian, Short Legs!
Second son! And his servants…
Why do boys and girls
have to play together?
It sucks that I have to be
on the same team as him!
The second son.
Father's mission target's son…
Being friends with him
will benefit us like crazy.
What are you looking at?
But he's mean to me, so I don't like him.
I don't have time to be
bothered by a pest like you!
A pest?!
I have to become an MVP
and receive a Stella in this tournament!
I have to become an Imperial Scholar
like my brother… Or else…
Father will never notice me.
W… Wait, Mr. Damian!
Gather round!
Since your Physical Education teacher,
Mr. Bobby, is out sick,
I'll be in charge of this class today.
Keep up the gentlemanly
and lady-like spirit,
and play with elegance!
Okay!
We will now have
an interclass dodgeball game
between Class Three, Cecil Dormitory
and Class Four, Wald Dormitory!
Begin!
MISSION:10 THE GREAT DODGEBALL PLAN
Let's get them, Mr. Damian!
You can do it, Damian!
Mr. Damian!
I got you information on Class Four!
Let's see.
The only way to receive a Stella
is for me to become an MVP.
My enemy… is him!
In order to win this tournament
against Class Four,
I have to get rid of him first!
Ha!
Son of a Command Sergeant Major,
Bill Watkins!
Nice catch, Bill!
What is that monster?!
There's no way he's the same age as us!
It's him…
Magic Bullet Bill!
With his excellent physique
and intelligence,
he has won numerous ball game tournaments
since his kindergarten days!
Are there even
that many tournaments in kindergarten?!
It's dangerous
wearing your glasses, old man!
Thanks for your concern,
Chairman's son, Damian.
But I won't get hit so don't worry. Also…
Any hits above the shoulders don't count.
Confirmation of enemy position.
Good airflow, humidity, and offset.
-Ugh.
-Umph.
Four players out.
-What?! Seriously?!
-Good job, Bill!
Don't be afraid! It was just luck!
That was no luck.
My ball
is perfectly calculated.
I did more than just simulation training.
I physically trained for this as well.
-My son, Bill.
-Yes, Daddy!
You are Eden's, no, the man who will
eventually become the Army's hero.
Grab the Stella with your hand!
For the future of Ostania!
Sir, yes, sir!
Yes…
It's already decided that I'll win.
Wait! If we get hit by that, we'll die!
Don't worry. I'll go easy on women.
Well, that pisses me off too!
Out.
Talking quite big, huh?
You don't think we have our own plan?
You big monster.
Dodgeball…
isn't something you can win on your own!
Yeah!
Ouch!
Reach for the MVP!
We're going to become the MVP!
Come on! Formation G!
Yeah!
Four players out.
We're not done!
Shadow Offshoot
Attack!
Offshoot, huh?
An Offshoot…
looks like this!
Mr. Damian. It made me happy
to be able to be by your side.
Emile!
I know all your
good characteristics, Mr. Damian.
I can't think of any right now, but…
I'm sure there was something.
Please win, Mr. Damian!
Because Mr. Damian,
you'll always be our MVP!
The forbidden face block!
Emile!
Emile! Hey!
Ewen, idiot. Don't cry.
I'm not crying!
-…Until the end…
-Hm?
Don't lose hope until the end!
Yeah! Yeah, I know!
If I give up, the game will end there--
Damn it! At this pace, we'll lose!
I have to somehow get him
at his weakest point!
I don't care how much
the others are defeated.
I just need to win and stand out!
The second son is such a jerk.
Next is…
that little one.
I'll aim for… her legs!
Oh! He missed! How lucky!
Pass the ball!
She jumped even before I threw!
Take this!
Then next, I'll aim for her right arm!
Then her left!
Then it's time for my secret move!
This ball rapidly changes its trajectory,
and it will pursue and catch
those who are running away from it!
Homing Slider
Shoot!
I thought you went easy on girls!
Ugh!
Out.
No way! She's reading my moves!
She's totally reading my pitch!
Who is that girl?!
-You're pretty good.
-Hm.
Etymology of dodgeball…
"Dodge" means to evade quickly.
What an elegant evasion.
Anya! Be careful of the outfielders!
Idiot! Hurry up and stand up!
Even you won't be able to run
from that position!
Die!
That bastard threw
everything he had in him!
It's unfortunate, but it's her fault
for being clumsy.
Don't worry. I'll stay behind
and lead Class Three to victory.
Out.
Wh… What are you doing, Mr. Damian?!
Huh! Oh, shoot! The MVP!
-Did you protect Anya?
-Huh?
Are you a good guy?
N… N… No!
I was just fed up getting defeated by
his ball so I wanted to try and catch it!
Damn it. You're the only one left.
I'm leaving it to you!
The future is in Anya's hands.
Now is the time
to unleash the killer shot!
Anya, this is my last advice to you.
The trick to pitching
is to use the whole body.
Think of this ball as a lightning arrow!
I won't let his death go to waste.
I'm not dead!
Anya will take revenge!
That power when she punched me…
She might just be able to!
I don't know what's going on,
but I feel some immense power.
Just maybe!
What's important is to shift your weight,
step out firmly, twist your hips
and transfer that force to your hands!
And then your hands… Um… Um… Anyway!
Killer Shot Star Catcher!
Game set.
Yay! We won!
Huh?
With this,
you'll definitely get the Stella, Bill!
Hm? Stella?
There's no way we'd give you one
for a little game that's part of class.
-Who said such a thing?
-Huh?
Rather, I should give you
a Tonito for yelling "die"
during the game.
Don't worry, Bill!
Let's do our best next time!
There'll be another chance!
But the spirit of those who have been
at odds with each other,
joining forces to face difficulties,
deserves a Stella, boys and girls.
Are you freaking serious?!
What's with that awful shot?!
-What a waste to have protected you!
-No way!
What?! You couldn't hit him either!
-I don't like you after all.
-Huh?!
What did you say, Short Legs?!
You can't say that to girls!
Maybe not…
Mother's teachings were pointless.
MISSION:11 STELLA
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi